[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUNE] You also like
leftover rice?
Hey! Save some for me!
[JUNE] Here.
Ima-Asim Homemade Vinegar.
If you make a sour face,
you're mine.
[PHONE CHIMES]
"You should get your things."
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Dear,
your father never treated you
like you're not his.
That's true.
And I know that he loved me too.
He never once failed
in making me feel otherwise.
Then...
why are you still so blue?
Ima, I miss Ping.
Have you really fallen
in love with him?
But...
I'm not sure if he feels
the same way for me.
Ima,
he has shown me everything,
all of his kindness.
I'm still so confused, Ima.
I don't know if it's because
I'm Don Nato's heir...
or because it's actually real.
Why don't you ask him then?
But I don't know how
to face him anymore!
He just thinks...
that I'm money-obsessed.
Look at the message he sent me.
Huh? He's asking you to come!
Ima, there are no emojis!
There's no GIF!
Meaning, he doesn't have
feelings for me anymore.
Darling, hold on.
Didn't you already put
everything on the line
when you haven't
fallen for him yet before
just for money?
Why don't you try
risking it all again?
You have nothing to lose!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]